It's a morning when I woke up at 5:30, still dimly lit.
I got up, washed my face, brushed my teeth and took care of my skin.
I notice the dryness of the room these days when I feel discomfort in my throat and ears.
I am wondering if I should buy a humidifier.
When the new year starts,
I was thinking of learning something physical... 😓
I'm happy with just watching YouTube and doing some simple stretches to feel like I'm getting something off my back!
I've heard that if you change the time you write in your journal from night to morning, the content will also change.
I have a list of words I've come across, things to do, mumbo-jumbo in my mind, and
There's no set format, I just write whatever comes to my mind.
Today I made an ideal time schedule for morning activities.
The other day I put on a pair of denims that I quickly took from the washing machine and went outside.
The hem was so wrinkled.
I spent the rest of the day wishing no one would look at my feet.
This skirt also comes with a bitter memory that I noticed a furball after I came home after wearing it.
I have a replacement blade for my hairball remover, but I have not been able to change the blade because the cap is no longer removable.
I'll try to get as far as I can today.
I've been thinking a lot about hairballs, ironing these days...
I've already had a satisfying day today, being able to do home cleaners.
It went by faster than I thought it would.
The sun is shining and it's getting brighter.
It's more eye-opening to be out in the sun.
When it's light outside, I finally get dressed and
It's like the day is starting in earnest.
I make a smoothie with frozen kiwi for breakfast.
I add a pinch of salt to 100cc of amazake and heat it up.
Add two kiwis and stir.
Slightly warm smoothie is ready.
This cupboard doesn't fit in the kitchen, so I'm using it here.
It's still a little inconvenient if it's not right next to the kitchen. 😂
I bought a great bouquet of recycled flowers from some event!
I had a bunch of them on display.
I still felt they were too jammed together, so I decided to separate them.😹
I love the weak scent of the candles when I pass by them.
I also like the delicate glass that seems to break.🥰
It's a spoon whose handle doesn't stick to the condiment.🐤
For some reason, my honey jar has been sticky lately, even after wiping it down.
I found just the cutest jar.
I was so distressed that I put the expiration date on the bottom of the jar.
I put off washing the canisters and started the new year.
I put a teaspoon in the salt and a tablespoon in the sugar.
I accidentally put a cutting board on a still warm induction heating.
I warped the wooden cutting board.
I bought a new cutting board.
I'm still getting used to the new place, and there are a lot of things I want to review here and there, such as storage and what I'm using.
It's been about a month in the blink of an eye, lol.
My sister gave me an avocado cutter as a gift.
I think the avocado was too soft.
When I cooked junk sandwich,
I wanted to set it with fries anyway.
Put the potatoes in a bag.
1 tablespoon each of flour and potato starch.
Add salt and white pepper and shake.
Put them in the oil before heating and fry them over medium heat.
Crispy and flaky fries inside.
If you eat a handful, you'll lose a lot in no time. 🤤
like I feel like I'm on a trip abroad,
Or a brunch complete with an amount of food that will make me feel like I'm about to start a party...
I was watching the drama while I was eating, and I was horrified at myself for almost eating it all.
I saved the rest for breakfast tomorrow.
I knew it was too early for a cold latte, so I heated it up in the microwave.☕😅
I've always longed to use a glass pen.
I suddenly saw an ad on Instagram for a glass pen kit and
I found myself buying one.
It also comes with a watercolor pen set that allows me to draw botanical art.
It's very helpful for me, as I don't have the artistic ability, to have drafts to practice with.😂
I lost track of time and just kept moving on to the next step.
In no time at all, the sun was setting and the room was getting cold.
That's all for now, and I'll see you next time.
I'm going to make dashi stock with a dashi packet and prepare dinner for the evening.
Cut 40g each of burdock root and carrot into 1cm cubes.
80 g chicken meat.
Put dried shiitake mushrooms back in water overnight.
(In the video I only put them back in for 30 minutes.😂)
Heat 1 teaspoon of oil and fry the chicken first.
Add 1 cup of soup stock
Add shiitake mushroom stock
1/2 teaspoon salt, 1 teaspoon sugar, 1 tablespoon light soy sauce
Cut fried tofu in half, swabbed and flipped over.
Two rice cakes left over from New Year's.
200㏄
Add water if it is not enough
Bring to a boil over medium heat and when bubbles start to appear.
Stir from the bottom.
Cover and cook over low heat for 10 minutes
100g ground pork, 1 tablespoon sake, 1 1/2 tablespoons soy sauce, 1/2 tablespoon sugar.
Mix together and put on heat
100 g chopped onion
(I substituted leeks)
1/2 cup soup stock, 300g potatoes
Make miso soup with the rest of dashi broth.
A cup of white miso for dressing and a spoonful for miso soup.
I also add some leftover avocado from the morning.
When the potatoes are cooked, mash them.
Mix mayonnaise with white soybean paste.
When the potatoes are heated through, stuff them into fried tofu.
I made a lot of it and ate it for three days.
If I reheat it on the fish grill, the fried bean curd gets crispy and it's good all the way through.
Add salt and boil quickly.
Kitsune croquettes with deep-fried tofu instead of batter.
I liked how easy and crispy they were to fry and how easy they were to wash.
White miso, mayonnaise, cheese
This recipe went well with bitter spring vegetables!
burdock root are good smell.
It was a menu that filled me up.
I finished breakfast with yesterday's leftovers.
I'm rearranging the drawers that have been bothering me for a long time.
I was thinking of moving it to a larger storage area because it's overflowing with cutlery.
I decided to try a diagonal storage case because it looked like a good idea.
perfect fit.
Every time I open the drawer my heart is soothed 🥰 lol
I'd better leave the wooden spoons outside.
I decided to put it in the empty jar for now.
I have to be careful not to lose the case that's provided.
I can't go wrong with salted kelp in sweet zenzai.
Thank you for watching to the end!